stimul-cash.com 2014-05-26

# Stimul-Cash.com Affiliate Program

Stimul-Cash.com has created this privacy policy to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy of our Affiliate Program members (affiliates). Please read the following to familiarize yourself with our privacy policy, and how we treat all personal information collected from our affiliates.

##  What this Privacy Policy Covers

This privacy policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information collected by us through a website owned and operated by us.

This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies that are not in our direct subjection, or of persons not employed by us, including any third-party content contributors bound by contract and any third-party websites to which our websites may link.

##  Collection and Use of Personal Information

You may visit our websites without revealing any personal information. However, we do need certain personal information if you wish to register an Affiliate Account, receive our newsletter, or use some of our other services.

If and where required, this information may include your contact information and/or your company contact information. We will use this information to reply to your inquiries, to provide you with requested products and services, to set up your members account, to contact you regarding new products and services, and to make financial settlements.

By accessing our services and voluntarily providing us with the personal information we request, you consent to the collection and use of information in accordance with this privacy policy.

##  Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information

We automatically receive and record certain types of non-personal information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page you requested. We may use this information to customize the advertising and content you see and to fulfill your requests for certain products and services. However, we do not connect this non-personal data to any personal information we hold about you.

We also allow third party companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. These cookies are not connected to any personal information. Third party cookie usage is subject to their own privacy policies, and we assume no responsibility or liability for their use.

##  Information Sharing and Disclosure

We will not disclose your personal information to any third parties who work on our behalf to provide products and services requested by you. We will not share your personal information for any purposes even if a third parties privacy policies are consistent with ours.

We may otherwise disclose your personal information when: (a) We have your express consent to share the information for a specified purpose; (b) We need to respond to subpoenas, court orders or other such legal process; (c) We find that your actions on our websites violate our Terms and Conditions document or any of our usage guidelines pertaining to corresponding products or services.

We may also disclose your personal information, with your consent, to a third party payment gateway when it is absolutely required to allow us to make financial settlements. However, only information that you provide in the Payment Method section of the Affiliate Account settings will be shared. It is your responsibility to provide the minimum but sufficient information needed to permit us to make a timely settlement.

##  Consent

If you do not consent to the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information as outlined in this policy, please do not provide any personal information to us. If you have provided personal information to us and cease to consent to its use or disclosure as outlined herein, please notify us at [support@stimul-cash.com](mailto:support@stimul-cash.com).

After proper identification and fulfillment of such a request your personal data will be deleted from our records and from our backup infrastructure. However, records of payments may remain with third party payment companies such as banks, e-wallets and other payments operators . This may or may not include your personal information.

##  Security

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be considered 100% secure. but your information stored on our systems is protected for your privacy and security. In certain areas of our websites, as identified on the site, we use industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.

We also safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access, through access control procedures, network firewalls and physical security measures.

Further, we retain your personal information only as long as is necessary to fulfill the purposes identified above.   

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may at any time, without notice to you, and with sole discretion, amend this policy from time to time. It is in your own interest to review this policy periodically. Your continued use of our websites after any such amendments signifies your acceptance thereof.

##  Questions or Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions about this privacy policy, or the security of your own personal information, please e-mail us at [support@stimul-cash.com](mailto:support@stimul-cash.com).
